ACTWU's National Textile Recruitment and Training Program Records 5619/034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- James C. Murray Teacher New Jersey, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Linda Breen (Teacher) Terminated, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Teacher Marco Aranguiz (Miami, Fla.), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Paid: Invoices National Overhead, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  July 1978
- Joint Boards- Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board. Walt Rainey, Mgr., 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Local 281 H. Mercer, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Garden Spot Joint Board Carl Frazier, Mgr., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- North Jersey Joint Board Jim Dillon, Manager, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Local 7587, ACTWU Frank Lucas Business Agent, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Joint Board. Jack Couty, Manager, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Memphis Area Joint Board Don Warner, International Representative, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Synthetic Division, ACTWU Bruce Dunton, Director, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Supportive Training (Worksheets), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Everlon (Travel Folder), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence Synthetic Division, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Brochure, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Staff Meeting, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Jim Clark, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Meeting with Kilgallon, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Bruce Raynor Signature File, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Dale Belman, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Clayola Brown, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Camille Robinson, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Prospects for New Contract, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Bingham Graves, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Bruce Raynor Staff Mtg., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- NTRTP Follow-Up, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Oneita Knitting Mills, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Lawrence, Mass., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Gold Mills, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Negotiations- Raybestos Manhattan Industrial Company, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Raybestos Manhattan Industrial Company & ACTWU, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- ACTWU Synthetic Fibers Division [folder 1 of 4], 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Synthetic Fibers Division [folder 2 of 4], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Synthetic Fibers Division [folder 3 of 4], 1967-1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Synthetic Fibers Division [folder 4 of 4], 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- New Proposal, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  May 1978
- ACTWU Synthetic Fibers Division, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Training Program New Proposal [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Training Program New Proposal [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Craddock Terry Union Mtg. Newsletter Co., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- ACTWU Textile Division, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women & NYC Visitor's Bureau, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Intakes for q/e, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  6/30/1978
- Intakes for q/e, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  9/30/1978
- Intakes for q/e, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Intakes for q/e, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  3/30/1979
- Testing, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- ESL/General Information, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Korean Brochure
- Attendance sheets, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Equipment Instructions and Warranties, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- NTRTP/Misc., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- NTRTP Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Paperback Library, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Budget/Supportive Training Worksheet no.1, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Budget/Supportive Training Worksheet no.2, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Budget/Supportive Training Current Projection, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Service & Allied Industry/ESL (Spanish), 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  English and Spanish
- Meadville Attendance Sheets, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Berkshire-Hathaway/ New Bedford ESL (Portuguese) Joan Howland and Manny Aguiar, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Close Out Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Fall River Textile-Clothing ESL (Portuguese) Kathy Lund, John Santos, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Greater New York Joint Board/ESL Linda Breen, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Greater New York Joint Board/GED Peter Agree and Charles Brennan, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Intakes for Quarter Ending, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Intakes for Quarter Ending, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Intakes for Quarter Ending, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  3/30/1978
- Intakes: Close out for Contract, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Invoices/processed, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Knoxville/GED June Rostan Bingham Graves, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Knoxville Curriculum Project, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- The Science Test, The Unions, The Grievance Procedure and Arbitration, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- The University of Chicago Collective Bargaining Instructor's Manual, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- NTRTP Classroom Program, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Budget, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  August 1978
- Budget, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  June 1978
- Teacher Peter A. Agree New York, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Teacher Linda Breen, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Teacher Isboseth Burgos, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Teacher Fred Ciporen NYC, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Teacher Ludovic Dauphin NYC, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Teacher Nhu-Lang Fowler, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Teacher Edy Gauvin New York, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Teacher Marcia Gail Lesser, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Teacher Elaine Olivera, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Teacher Joe O'Neill New Bedford, Mass, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Teacher Nicolas Orlandi Union City, NJ, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Teacher Nancy Pontes New Bedford, Mass, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Local 169/ESL (Spanish) Teacher Cathy Armistead, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Local 748T, Houston Math,ESL (Spanish, Vietnamese) Pisciella, Longknife, Ngo, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  English and Vietnamese
- Local 2052/ESL (Spanish) Teacher Jim Murray, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- NTRTP Classroom Program Quarterly Narrative Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- New Bedford Textile-Clothing ESL (Portuguese) Howland, Aguiar, O'Neill, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- New Haven/GED Teacher John Flannelly, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Local 694, Miami/ESL (Spanish) Teacher Ana Roca, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- NTRTP/General Information, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Williamsburg, Va., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Current Projection, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Budget, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  March 1979
- Basic Education/ GED Curriculum, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Budget, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  April 1979
- Amalgamated Service & Allied Industries/ GED, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Greater New York Joint Board/ ESL (Spanish), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Local 1733/ ATP Processors ESL Paterson, N.J., 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- New Bedford/ ESL (Portuguese), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Local 1908/ESL (Spanish) Closter, N.J., 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Philadelphia Textile Workers Joint Board ESL, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Knoxville/ GED Teacher June Rostan, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Fall River/ ESL (Portuguese), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  English and Portuguese
- Amalgamated Service & Allied Industries/ ESL (Spanish), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Local 169/ESL (Spanish) NYC, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Service & Allied Industries/ESL (Haitian-French), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  English and French
- Local 694, Miami ESL (Spanish), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Local 444/ Brooklyn Quilting ESL (Spanish), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Local 1665 Allentown, Pa. ESL (Spanish-Vietnamese), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Local 2052/ESL (Spanish), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- NTRTP Classroom Program/Misc., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Institute of Social Studies Rand School of Social Science, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  Fall 1954
- Training Aids for Teaching Stewards Training, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Collective Bargaining Materials, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- NTRTP Programs Other Info. Teacher List, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Classroom Program Reports Narrative Report, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- NTRTP Calendars, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Salary Pay Sheet Summer Teacher, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Coordinator Activity Reports, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Highlander, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- NTRTP Graduates, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- NTRTP & ACTWU Expense Sheets, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- NTRTP Priscilla Carrasquillo ESL Union City, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Luke Martin ESL Vietnamese Allentown, Pa, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Nathaniel Maxwell Metrics Charleston, S.C. (Saturday class), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Ellen Agree ESL, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Albert Bichner Philadelphia Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Isboseth Burgos ESL North Jersey Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Linda Corbin GED (Opelika, Ala.), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Ludovic Dauphin GED NY, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Priscilla Carrasquillo ESL Union City Local 2052, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Thea Erener Typing 99 University Place, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Linda Garcia ESL 99 University Place NY Joint Board, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Florence Grant Metrics Local 1836 Charleston, S.C., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Larry Gammage ESL Vietnamese, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Barbara Lawrence GED, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Guillermo Perez ESL Miami, Florida, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Ross O'Laughlin, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- David Ramos (Citizenship), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- June Rostan Highlander Rome, GA, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Marco Zanoni Philadelphia Joint Board, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- William Shell Local 1840, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Grace Roberts Allentown, Pa ESL, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Martha Breedlove, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Louis Santiago, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Mary Evans, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Jacqui Lupo, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Convention Expenses Hotel Bill, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Avon Knitting Mills, N.J., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Ballet Fabrics, Inc. Program 5, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Fleisher Finishing, Inc. Program 5, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Craftex Mills of Pa., Inc. Program 5, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Lorbrook Corporation Program 5, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Mosseri National Ind. Perth Amboy, N.J., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  5/28/1980
- Putnam-Harzel Finishing Co., Inc. Canal St., Putnam, Conn., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  8/4/1980
- Roselin Mfg. Co., Inc. Willimantic, Conn., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Warrington Woolen, Inc., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- A. Wimpeheimer & Sons, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- 4th Contract- Proposal, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- National Text Recruit & Training Program, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Committee for Women in N-T Trades, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Forms Preparation Handbook US Department of Labor, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- De Poortere & Spencer, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- Manpower Training Program, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Internal Reports Contract 4, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Janice Williams, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Jacqui, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 82)
- Follow-Up Union, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 83)
- Follow-Up Subcontractors, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 84)
- Labor Studies Center Degree Program, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 85)
- Films Women & General, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Babbies & Banners (Premier), 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- DePoortere Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- DePoortere Corporation Coordinator Activity Report Sub-Contractor Background Proposal, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- DePoortere Corporation Union Correspondence, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- DePoortere Corporation Contract, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- CLUW Convention Committee, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- CLUW New York Exec. Board, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Susan Plante, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Northeastern Summer School, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Worth Textile Sylvester, Ga. Graph Sheet, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Worth Textile Contract, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Worth Textile Intakes, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Worth Textile Coordinator Activity Report Sub-contractor background Prop., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Worth Textile Company Correspondence, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Modern Filters (Graph Sheets plus Status of Training Report), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Modern Filters (Contract), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Modern Filters (Union Correspondence), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Quarterly Reports, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  5/28/1981
- Packaging Division Union Correspondence, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Packaging System, Contract, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Textile Workers Union, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Manpower Project Immediate Material, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Retention Analysis, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Retention Survey, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- NTRTP Staff, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- OJT-Budget & Salaries Review/ Projections, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Active, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- NTRTP Staff Job Descriptions, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Robert James Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Bobbie McGee- Narrative Report, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Proposal, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Priscilla Carrasquillo, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Karin Gerstel Education Coordinator, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Carlos Lopez Car Accident Case, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Carlos Lopez NTRTP Field Coordinator, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- NTRTP Staff, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Reports to be Typed, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Proposal, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Howard Brown, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Shelly Winograd Synthetics Division Field Coordinator, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Connie D. Simmons, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Lou Pichinson, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Bobbie McGee Educational Coordinator, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- NTRTP Education, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Thomasina Myers Hutchins Education Coordinator, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Priscilla Carrasquillo, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Priscilla Carrasquillo Correspondence, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Paid: Invoices Supportive Training, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  May 1, 1977- May 28, 1978
- Camille Y. Robinson's NTRTP Data [folder 1 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Camille Y. Robinson's NTRTP Data [folder 2 of 3], 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Camille Y. Robinson's NTRTP Data [folder 3 of 3], 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Government Furniture Papers, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- NTRTP Forms CETA Program Status Summary, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- NTRTP Summary & Contracts, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Job Training (On the Job), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- On-the-Job Training, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Manpower Training Proposal, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Property, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- American Federation of Government Employees, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Close-Out 99-6-672-92-11, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Harold Rieve Jim Clark NTRTP Proposal, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Close-out Emmanuel Sandi, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Quarterly Report, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Quarterly Report, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  5/30-12/31/1980
- 5th Contract Quarterly Report, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  6/30/1980
- How to do Government Quarterly Reports - NTRTP, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- NTRTP H. Brown (confidential), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  12/19/1980
- Emmanuel Sandi Administrative Coordinator, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Retention Survey, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Reports, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  3-31-1981
- Retention Survey, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Howard Brown, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Jim Clark- US Department of Labor, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Fernando Allegria, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Avtex, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Amerbelle Corp., 1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Annual Report of Detailed Characteristics, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Contract 99-8-672-92-17, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Contract 3 99-8-672-92-17, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Projections, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Opening & Close-Out Contract 99-7-672-92-14, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Contract 99-7-672-92-14, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Contract 99-6-672-92-11, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Jim Clark, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- NTRTP, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Ballet Fabrics, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Forms-Participants, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- ASAI-Citizenship, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Report Membership List, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Memphis Area Joint Board CETA, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Contract 4, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Current NTRTP, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Attendance Sheets, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  October/November
- Shoe Merger, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Close-Out References, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Cost Over-Runs, Previous Contracts, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Howard Brown, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Staff & Payroll, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- OJT-Costs & Projections, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Forms Award/Contract, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Budget Projections, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Labor Dept. Misc. Correspondence Calls, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Proposals- Textile Recruitment + Training Program, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Staff Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Kilgallon, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Contractor's Costs, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Attendance Reports, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  June & July 1980
- Attendance Reports, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  August & September 1980
- Attendance Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  December 1980- January 1981
- Attendance Reports, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  February-March 1981
- Program no.5 Contract 99-9-2181-92-24, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Opening + Close-Out 99-0-2181-92-24, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Shelley Winograd, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Lou Pichinson, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Priscilla Carrasquillo, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Carlos Lopez NTRTP, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Emanuel J. Sandi, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Karin Gertsel, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Yvonne Cohen, 1976-1981 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Connie D. Simmons, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Mary F. O'Mahoney, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Program no.5 Costs Statement, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- NTRTP Contracts Locations & Disbursements, 1976-1981 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Avon Knitting Mills, Inc. Graph Sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Avon Knitting Mills, Inc. Intakes, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Riveredge Warping and Processing Graph Sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Riveredge Warping and Processing Correspondence, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Riveredge Warping and Processing (Contract), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Riveredge Warping Company Coordinator Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Clifton Yarn Mills (Correspondence), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc. Coordinator Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc. Graph Sheet, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc. Contract, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Chromatex Correspondence, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Chromatex Graph Sheet Trainee Info, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Chromatex Contract, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Chromatex Coordinator Activity Reports, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Hugh-Nelson Columbia Carpet Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Hugh-Nelson Columbia Carpet Graph Sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- C. Cosentino Co., Inc. Intakes, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- C. Cosentino, Inc. Graph Sheets, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- C. Cosentino, Inc. Correspondence, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- C. Cosentino, Inc. Contract, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Kalkstein Silk Mills Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Kalkstein Silk Mills Trainee Record, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Putnam-Herzl Intakes, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Putnam-Herzl Correspondence for Company, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Putnam-Herzl, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Putnam-Herzl Correspondence for Union, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Putnam-Herzl Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Jomac Inc. Intakes, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Jomac Inc. Graph Sheet, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Jomac, Inc. Warrington Contract, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Jonathan Temple Communications, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Jonathan Temple Contract, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Jonathan Temple Intakes, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Jefferies Processors Intakes, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Jefferies Processors Contract, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Jefferies Processors Graph Sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Anchor Dye and Finishing Co. Intakes, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Anchor Dye and Finishing Co. Union Correspondence, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Anchor Dye and Finishing Co. Contract, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Anchor Dye and Finishing Co. Coordinator Activity Report, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- NTRTP Forms, Originals, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Memos, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Allied Industries, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Department of Labor, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Department of Labor, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Department of Labor, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Department of Labor, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- NTRTP Proposal, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Memos to H. Brown, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Southern Region, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- South Carolina Coastal Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Tidewater Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Rhode Island Joint Board, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Southern New England Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Synthetic Division Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- A/P Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- NTRTP New Contract, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Fernando Alegria, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Correspondence DOI, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Kilgallon, 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Twin Cities Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Upper South Region Tidewater Joint Board, ACTWU, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Local 2052 Union City, New Jersey, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- NTRTP Correspondence, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Worksheets Request Funds Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- North New Jersey Joint Board, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Bi-County Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Central Massachusetts Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Cincinnati Joint Board Textile, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Highlander Research & Education Center, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Greater Northern Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- GTA Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Penn-Keystone Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Memphis Area Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Mid-West Region Indiana-Kentucky Joint Board, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- New England Region, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Northeastern Massachusetts Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Ohio Joint Board Cleveland, Toledo, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- W-4 Payroll Forms, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Amerbelle Corp. Company Correspondence, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Amerbelle Corp. Intakes, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- Training Program Completions, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  6/30/1981
- Classroom Program- Narrative Report, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Quarterly Reports, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  12/30/1979
- Total Completions Column D,E,F,G, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 64)